Guide to the H. Lee Waters Film Collection, 1936-2005, bulk 1936-1942 RL.10075
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Movies of Local People, 1936-1942; 50 Linear Feet
  - Gastonia (N.C.)
    - Gastonia (N.C.), 1940; 24
      - 1940 (Reel 1), TRT 00:14:48
        - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 2 (Box 4, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0031)
      - 1940 (Reel 2), TRT 00:15:21
        - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 2 of 2 (Box 4, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0032)
      - Preservation tape master, 3/4 inch Umatic (Box 28, Video-cassette RL10075-Umatic-0012)
    - 1942, TRT 00:29:15
      - Digital HD+ preservation scan of reversal original RL10075-F16-0033 (Digital-materials RL10075-SET-0004, Video-file RL10075-F16-0033_3k.mov)
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., col., reel 1 of 1 (Box 4, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0033)
        Preservation
        Sent to AV Geeks for migration to digital file, September, 2014. Returned from AVGeeks with raw video and MP4 files, September 17, 2014.
  - Granite Falls (N.C.)
    - circa 1938 (Reel 1), TRT 00:13:00
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 4 (Box 4, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0034)
      - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 4 (Box 22, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0185)
      - Preservation tape master, betacam sp, reels 1, 3, and 4 of 4 (Box 27, Video-cassette RL10075-Bcam-0001)
      - Preservation tape master, digital betacam, reels 1, 3, and 4 of 4 (Box 27, Video-cassette RL10075-Dbcam-0002)
      - Shot list, reels 1, 2, and 4. (Box 33)
      - DVD master (Box 35, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0006)
      - DVD master, Reels 1, 3, 4 (Box 35, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0007)
    - circa 1938 (Reel 2)
      - circa 1938 (Reel 2 b&w sequence), TRT 00:11:32
        - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, col., reel 2 of 4 (Box 4, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0035)
        - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 2 of 4 (Box 14, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0116)
      - circa 1938 (Reel 2 color sequence), TRT 00:01:21
        - Color separation negative, 16 mm, si., col., reel 2 of 4 (Box 14, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0117)
      - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, col., reel 2 of 4 (Box 22, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0186)
      - Preservation tape master, digital betacam, reel 2 of 4 (Box 28, Video-cassette RL10075-Dbcam-0008)
    - circa 1938 (Reel 3), TRT 00:13:04
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 3 of 4 (Box 4, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0036)
      - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 3 of 4 (Box 22, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0187)
    - circa 1938 (Reel 4), TRT 00:12:04
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 4 of 4 (Box 2, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0017)
      - Digital 10-bit 2K preservation scan of reversal original RL10075-F16-0017 (Digital-materials RL10075-SET-0020, Video-file RL10075-F16-0017.mkv)
      - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 4 of 4 (Box 20, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0176)
    - circa 1941-1942 (Reel 1), TRT 00:40:00
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, col., reel 1 of 1 (Box 4, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0037)
      - Internegative, 16 mm, si., col., reel 1 of 1 (Box 14, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0118)
      - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, col., reel 1 of 1 (Box 22, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0188)
      - Preservation tape master, digital betacam (Box 28, Video-cassette RL10075-Dbcam-0008)
      - DVD master (Box 35, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0006)
  - Greensboro (N.C.)
    - circa 1939 (Reel 1), TRT 00:21:23
    - Digital 10-bit 2K preservation scan of reversal original RL10075-F16-0038 (Digital-materials RL10075-SET-0005, Video-file RL10075-F16-0038.mkv)
    - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 5, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0038)
    - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 14, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0119)
    - Preservation tape master, betacam sp (Box 29, Video-cassette RL10075-Bcam-0007)
    - DVD master (Box 36, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0031)
    - Shot list. (Box 34)
  - Henderson (N.C.)
    - circa 1938 (Reel 1), TRT 00:32:49
    - Digital 2K preservation scan of reversal original RL10075-F16-0076 (Digital-materials RL10075-SET-0006, Video-file RL10075-F16-0076_H lee Waters Henderson 1938.mov)
    - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Oversize-film-can 9, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0076)
    - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 14, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0120)
    - Preservation tape master, 3/4 inch Umatic (Box 27, Video-cassette RL10075-Umatic-0001)
    - Preservation tape master, digital betacam (Box 29, Video-cassette RL10075-Dbcam-0009)
    - DVD master (Box 35, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0008)
    - Shot list (Box 34)
  - Jackson (N.C.)
    - 1939 (Reel 1), TRT 00:22:10
    - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 5, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0039)
    - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 22, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0189)
    - Preservation tape master, betacam sp (Box 29, Video-cassette RL10075-Bcam-0008)
    - Preservation tape master, digital betacam (Box 29, Video-cassette RL10075-Dbcam-0010)
    - DVD master (Box 35, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0012)
    - Shot list (Box 34)
  - Kannapolis (N.C.)
    - 1941 (Reel 1), TRT 00:34:52
      - Digital UHD+ preservation scan of reversal original RL10075-F16-0040 (Digital-materials RL10075-SET-0007, Video-file RL10075-F16-0040_HLeeWaters_KannapolisNC1941.mov)
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., col., reel 1 of 3 (Box 5, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0040)
      - Internegative, 16 mm, si., col., reel 1 of 3 (Box 14, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0121)
      - Screening print, 16 mm, si., col., reel 1 of 3 (Box 22, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0190)
      - Preservation tape master, digital betacam, reel 1 of 3 (Box 29, Video-cassette RL10075-Dbcam-0011)
      - DVD master, reel 1 of 3 (Box 35, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0009)
    - 1941 (Reel 2), TRT 00:55:18
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 2 of 3 (Oversize-film-can 8, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0063)
      - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 2 of 3 (Box 14, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0122)
      - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 2 of 3 (Box 22, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0191)
      - Preservation tape master, digital betacam, reel 2 of 3 (Box 29, Video-cassette RL10075-Dbcam-0012)
      - DVD master, reel 2 of 3 (Box 35, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0010)
    - 1941 (Reel 3), TRT 00:47:10
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 3 of 3 (Box 5, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0041)
      - Digital 10-bit 2K preservation scan of reversal original RL10075-F16-0041 (Digital-materials RL10075-SET-0007, Video-file RL10075-F16-0041_Kannapolis_Reel3_2K.mkv)
      - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 3 of 3 (Box 14, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0123)
      - Digital 10-bit 2K preservation scan of preservation internegative RL10075-F16-0123 (Digital-materials RL10075-SET-0007, Video-file RL10075-F16-0123.mkv)
      - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 3 of 3 (Box 22, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0192)
      - Digital 10-bit 2K preservation scan of screening print RL10075-F16-0192 (Digital-materials RL10075-SET-0007, Video-file RL10075-F16-0192.mkv)
      - Preservation tape master, betacam sp, reel 3 of 3 (Box 29, Video-cassette RL10075-Bcam-0009)
      - Preservation tape master, digital betacam, reel 3 of 3 (Box 29, Video-cassette RL10075-Dbcam-0013)
        Preservation note
        Sent to AV Geeks for migration to digital file, May 20, 2014. Returned from AV Geeks with raw video MOV and MP4 MOV, June 13, 2014. - Craig Breaden
        MD5: 88b504ca89656ed2fb5970aa97d8a187
      - Preservation tape master, digital betacam, reel 3 of 3, duplicate (Box 29, Video-cassette RL10075-Dbcam-0014)
      - Preservation tape master, digital betacam, reel 3 of 3, "edited highlights" (Box 29, Video-cassette RL10075-Dbcam-0015)
      - DVD master, reel 3 of 3 (Box 35, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0011)
    - Kannapolis (N.C.), circa 1936-1941; 32
      Screened on one of the following dates: 1936 July 30-31; 1936 September 09; 1938 May 12-13; 1940 August 29-30; 1941 February 06-07; 1941 October 01-02. Screened at one of the following theatres: Y.M.C.A. Theatre (1936); Colonial Theatre (1938); Dixie Theatre and Palace Theatre (1940, 1941 February);Swanee Theatre (1941 October).
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 5, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0042)
  - Lebanon (Va.)
    Individual identified as A.P. Baldwin appears at approximately 0:00:29 - 0:00:31, smiling and hiding from the camera behind another man. A.P. Baldwin was principal of Honaker High School in Honaker, VA.
    - 1940 (Reel 1), TRT 00:07:25
    - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 5, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0043)
    - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 15, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0125)
    - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 23, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0193)
    - Preservation tape master, betacam sp (Box 28, Video-cassette RL10075-Bcam-0006)
    - Preservation tape master, 3/4 inch Umatic (Box 29, Video-cassette RL10075-Umatic-0013)
    - DVD master (Box 36, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0032)
    - Shot list. (Box 34)
  - Lenoir (N.C.)
    - 1937 (Reel 1), TRT 00:22:02
    - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 5, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0044)
    - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 23, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0194)
    - Preservation tape master, betacam sp (Box 27, Video-cassette RL10075-Bcam-0001)
    - Preservation tape master, digital betacam (Box 27, Video-cassette RL10075-Dbcam-0002)
    - DVD master (Box 35, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0012)
  - Lexington (N.C.)
    - 1935-1953 (Reel 1), TRT 00:27:04
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 6, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0046)
      - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 15, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0126)
      - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 23, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0195)
      - Preservation tape master, digital betacam (Box 29, Video-cassette RL10075-Dbcam-0016)
      - VHS copy (Box 29, Video-cassette RL10075-VHS-0006)
      - DVD master (Box 35, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0013)
    - circa 1937-1945 (Reel 1), TRT 00:32:53
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 6, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0047)
      - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 15, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0127)
      - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 23, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0196)
      - Preservation tape master, digital betacam (Box 29, Video-cassette RL10075-Dbcam-0016)
      - VHS copy (Box 29, Video-cassette RL10075-VHS-0006)
      - DVD master (Box 35, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0013)
    - circa 1939-1943
      - Reel 1 of 2
        - Digital 10-bit 2K preservation scan of reversal original RL10075-F16-0250 (Digital-materials RL10075-SET-0008, Video-file RL10075-F16-0250.mkv)
        - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 2, TRT 01:08:55 1654 feet (Box 42, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0250)
      - Reel 2 of 2
        - Digital 10-bit 2K preservation scan of reversal original RL10075-F16-0251 (Digital-materials RL10075-SET-0008, Video-file RL10075-F16-0251.mkv)
        - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, color, reel 2 of 2, TRT 00:59:59 1440 feet (Box 42, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0251)
  - Liberty (N.C.), circa 1936-1939; 37
    Screened on one of the following dates: 1936 September 25-26; 1939 December 11-12. Screening Theatre: Curtis Theatre.
    - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, col., reel 1 of 1 (Oversize-film-can 3, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0027)
  - Lillington (N.C.)
    - circa 1939 (Reel 1), TRT 00:07:23
      - Digital 10-bit 2K preservation scan of preservation internegative RL10075-F16-0128 (Digital-materials RL10075-SET-0009, Video-file RL10075-F16-0128.mkv)
      - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 3 (Box 15, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0128)
      - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 (Box 23, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0197)
      - Preservation tape master, digibeta (Box 33, Video-cassette RL10075-Dbcam-0031)
      - DVD master, reels 1 and 2. (Box 36, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0040)
    - circa 1939 (Reel 2), TRT 00:21:33
      - Digital 10-bit 2K preservation scan of preservation internegative RL10075-F16-0129 (Digital-materials RL10075-SET-0009, Video-file RL10075-F16-0129.mkv)
      - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 2 of 3 (Box 15, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0129)
      - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 2 (Box 23, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0247)
    - circa 1939 (Reel 3), TRT 00:10:41
      - Digital 10-bit 2K preservation scan of reversal original RL10075-F16-0048 (Digital-materials RL10075-SET-0009, Video-file RL10075-F16-0048.mkv)
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, col., reel 3 of 3 (Box 6, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0048)
      - Preservation tape master, 3/4 inch Umatic, reel 3 of 3 (Box 29, Video-cassette RL10075-Umatic-0014)
      - DVD master, reel 3. (Box 36, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0033)
      - Shot list, reel 3. (Box 33)
  - Lockhart and Union (S.C.), 1937 September 27-28
    - DVD master, reels 1 and 2 (Box 36, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0055)
  - Louisburg (N.C.)
    - circa 1936-1937 (Reel 1), TRT 00:10:39
    - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 6, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0049)
    - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 15, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0130)
    - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 23, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0198)
    - Preservation tape master, digital betacam (Box 29, Video-cassette RL10075-Dbcam-0017)
    - DVD master, from internegative (Box 35, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0014)
  - Madison (N.C.), 1940 April 01; 40
    Screening Date: 1940 April 29-30. Screening Theatre: Patovi Theatre.
    - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 2 (Box 6, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0050)
    - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 2 of 2 (Box 6, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0051)
  - Madison (N.C.) and Mayodan (N.C.)
    - circa 1939-1941 (Reel 1), TRT 00:32:32
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., col., reel 1 of 3 (Box 6, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0052)
      - Digital 10-bit 2K preservation scan of reversal original RL10075-F16-0052 (Digital-materials RL10075-SET-0010, Video-file RL10075-F16-0052.mkv)
      - Internegative, 16 mm, si., col., reel 1 of 3 (Box 15, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0131)
      - Screening print, 16 mm, si., col., reel 1 of 3 (Box 24, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0200)
      - Preservation tape master, digital betacam, reels 1-2 of 3 (Box 30, Video-cassette RL10075-Dbcam-0018)
      - DVD master, reel 1 and 2 of 3, from internegative (Box 35, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0016)
    - circa 1939-1941 (Reel 2), TRT 00:39:35
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 2 of 3 (Box 7, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0054)
      - Digital 10-bit 2K preservation scan of reversal original RL10075-F16-0054 (Digital-materials RL10075-SET-0010, Video-file RL10075-F16-0054.mkv)
      - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 2 of 3 (Box 15, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0132)
      - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 2 of 3 (Box 24, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0201)
    - circa 1939-1941 (Reel 3), TRT 00:56:40
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 3 of 3 (Oversize-film-can 2, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0018)
      - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 3 of 3 (Oversize-film-can 12, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0107)
      - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 3 of 3 (Oversize-film-can 14, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0124)
      - Preservation tape master, digital betacam, reel 3 of 3 (Box 30, Video-cassette RL10075-Dbcam-0019)
      - DVD master, reel 3 of 3, from internegative (Box 35, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0017)
  - Martinsville (Va.)
    - circa 1937-1939 (Reel 1, 2), TRT 00:35:36
    - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 2 (Box 7, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0055)
    - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 2 of 2 (Box 7, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0056)
    - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reels 1-2 of 2 (Box 16, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0133)
    - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, reels 1-2 of 2 (Box 23, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0199)
    - Preservation tape master, digital betacam (Box 30, Video-cassette RL10075-Dbcam-0020)
    - DVD master, from internegative (Box 35, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0015)
  - Mooresville (N.C.)
    - circa 1937-1939 (Reel 1), TRT 00:43:18
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 2 (Box 7, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0058)
      - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 2 (Box 16, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0134)
      - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 2 (Box 24, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0202)
      - Preservation tape master, digital betacam (Box 30, Video-cassette RL10075-Dbcam-0021)
      - DVD master, from internegative (Box 35, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0018)
    - circa 1937-1939 (Reel 2), TRT 00:34:39
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 2 of 2 (Box 7, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0059)
      - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 2 of 2 (Box 16, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0135)
      - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 2 of 2 (Box 24, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0203)
  - Mount Airy (N.C.)
    - 1941 (Reel 1), TRT 00:26:14
    - VHS copy (Box 33, Video-cassette RL10075-VHS-0004)
    - DVD (Box 36, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0044)
    - Shot list. (Box 34)
  - Mount Holly (N.C.)
    - 1936, TRT 00:14:50
    - Digital 10-bit 2K preservation scan of reversal original RL10075-F16-0241 (Digital-materials RL10075-SET-0011, Video-file RL10075-F16-0241.mkv)
    - 16mm b&w reversal original, Moderate to advanced acetate decay. (Box 6, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0241)
    - 16mm b&w copy (Box 9, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0242)
    - DVD master (Box 36, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0052)
  - North Wilkesboro (N.C.)
    - 1937-1941 (Reel 1), TRT 00:44:58
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 2 (Oversize-film-can 6, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0053)
      - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 2 (Oversize-film-can 13, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0115)
      - Preservation tape master, betacam sp, reel 1 of 2 (Box 30, Video-cassette RL10075-Bcam-0010)
      - Shot list. (Box 34)
    - 1937-1941 (Reel 2), TRT 00:37:11
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, col., reel 2 of 2 (Oversize-film-can 5, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0045)
      - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 2 of 2 (Box 16, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0136)
      - Color separation negative, 16 mm, si., col., reel 2 of 2 (Box 16, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0137)
      - Preservation tape master, betacam sp, reel 2 of 2 (Box 30, Video-cassette RL10075-Bcam-0011)
      - Preservation tape master, betacam sp, color segments, reel 2 of 2 (Box 30, Video-cassette RL10075-Bcam-0012)
  - Oxford (N.C.)
    - 1938-1941 (Reel 1), TRT 00:36:24
    - Digital UHD preservation scan of preservation internegative RL10075-F16-0084 (Digital-materials RL10075-SET-0012, Video-file RL10075-F16-0084_01.266.avi, Video-file RL10075-F16-0084_02.268.avi)
    - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Oversize-film-can 7, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0060)
    - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Oversize-film-can 10, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0084)
    - Preservation tape master, betacam sp (Box 30, Video-cassette RL10075-Bcam-0013)
    - Shot list. (Box 34)
  - Pilot Mountain (N.C.)
    - circa 1939 (Reel 1), TRT 00:16:52
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 2 (Box 7, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0061)
      - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 2 (Box 16, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0138)
      - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 2 (Box 24, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0204)
      - Preservation tape master, digital betacam (Box 30, Video-cassette RL10075-Dbcam-0022)
      - DVD master, from internegative (Box 35, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0019)
    - circa 1939 (Reel 2), TRT 00:11:08
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 2 of 2 (Box 7, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0062)
      - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 2 of 2 (Box 16, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0139)
      - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 2 of 2 (Box 24, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0205)
  - Raeford (N.C.)
    - circa 1938 (Reel 1), TRT 00:22:21
    - Digital 2K preservation scan of original reversal film RL10075-F16-0064 (Digital-materials RL10075-SET-0016, Video-file RL10075-F16-0064.mkv)
    - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 (Box 8, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0064)
    - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 (Box 16, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0140)
    - Preservation tape master, betacam sp, reel 1 (Box 30, Video-cassette RL10075-Bcam-0014)
    - DVD (Box 36, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0045)
    - Shot list. (Box 34)
  - Red Springs (N.C.)
    - 1938, TRT 00:25:08
    - Betamax master (Box 41, Video-cassette RL10075-Bmax-0001)
  - Reidsville (N.C.), circa 1936-1942; 50
    Screening Date: unknown. Screening Theatre: unknown.
    - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 8, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0066)
  - Roxboro (N.C.)
    - circa 1936-1937 (Reel 1), TRT 00:15:53
      - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 17, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0141)
      - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 24, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0206)
      - Preservation tape master, betacam sp (Box 30, Video-cassette RL10075-Bcam-0015)
      - Preservation tape master, betacam sp, duplicate (Box 30, Video-cassette RL10075-Bcam-0016)
      - Preservation tape master, 3/4 inch Umatic (Box 31, Video-cassette RL10075-Umatic-0015)
      - Shot list. (Box 34)
    - circa 1936-1941 (Reel 1), TRT 00:19:31
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 8, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0075)
      - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 17, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0151)
      - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 25, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0212)
      - Preservation tape master, betacam sp (Box 30, Video-cassette RL10075-Bcam-0017)
      - Preservation tape master, betacam sp, duplicate (Box 31, Video-cassette RL10075-Bcam-0018)
      - Preservation tape master, 3/4 inch Umatic (Box 31, Video-cassette RL10075-Umatic-0021)
      - DVD master of timecode-embedded videotape (Box 36, Video-disc RL10075-DVD-0029)
    - circa 1937 (Reel 1), TRT 00:10:48
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 8, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0067)
      - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 17, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0142)
      - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 24, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0207)
      - Preservation tape master, betacam sp (Box 30, Video-cassette RL10075-Bcam-0015)
      - Preservation tape master, betacam sp, duplicate (Box 30, Video-cassette RL10075-Bcam-0016)
      - Preservation tape master, 3/4 inch Umatic (Box 31, Video-cassette RL10075-Umatic-0016)
      - Shot list. (Box 34)
    - 1938 (Reel 1), TRT 00:20:17
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 8, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0068)
      - Color separation, 16 mm, si., col., reel 1 of 1 (Box 8, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0069)
      - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 17, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0143)
      - Color separation negative, 16 mm, si., col., reel 1 of 1 (Box 17, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0144)
      - Screening print, 16 mm, si., b&w, col., reel 1 of 1 (Box 25, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0208)
      - Preservation tape master, betacam sp (Box 30, Video-cassette RL10075-Bcam-0015)
      - Preservation tape master, betacam sp, duplicate (Box 30, Video-cassette RL10075-Bcam-0016)
      - Preservation tape master, 3/4 inch Umatic (Box 31, Video-cassette RL10075-Umatic-0017)
      - Shot list. (Box 34)
    - 1939 (Reel 1), TRT 00:35:12
      - Reversal original, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 8, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0070)
      - Color separation, 16 mm, si., col., reel 1 of 1 (Box 8, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0071)
      - Internegative, 16 mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1 (Box 17, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0145)
      - Color separation negative, 16 mm, si., col., reel 1 of 1 (Box 17, Film-reel RL10075-F16-0146)